

Rairo M.

Python Developer

General info

Work experience Location

5 years total Harare, Zimbabwe

Time zone: UTC+2

Top technologies

Python	5+ years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
JavaScript	3 years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
Machine Learning	2 years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
PyTorch	2 years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
Natural Language Processing	2 years experience	1 2 3 4 5+

Technologies



Bio

Main areas of expertise

Python web development.

Main tech stack

- Python: >5 years of professional experience
- Flask: >3 years of professional experience
- React: >2 years of professional experience

Jobs of interest

I'm interested in Python developer jobs, where I work with my main technologies. I also have experience in Machine learning and would be interested in such roles.

Experience

Software Developer Contractor

11/2020 - now

Corporate Advisors, Canada (Remote)

2 years

- Machine Learning and Data Engineering with Python
- Postgres, React, GraphQL, Express web development.

Software Engineer

12/2018 - now

Initium Solutions

3 years and 11 months

Systems Development Consultant

07/2016 - 07/2017

Econet Wireless Zimbabwe

1 year

Education

Udacity
Nanodegree, Machine Learning Engineer

01/2020 - 12/2020

11 months

Udacity

01/2019 - 12/2019

Facebook PyTorch Scholarship Challenge

11 months

Treehouse

01/2015 - 12/2015

Android Development

11 months

Languages

English

Fluent

Shona

Native